# Jahdasha Flagg

# jahdasha.flagg@gmail.com 973.380.9638 | Newark, NJ

https://github.com/jahdasha l https://www.linkedin.com/in/jahdasha-flagg l http://jahdashaflagg.com/

Highly motivated front-end web developer able to build intricate and polished website with responsive interfaces. Proficient in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, APIs, AJAX, jQuery, Bootstrap and a host of JavaScript libraries as demonstrated in my in experience as front-end web developer.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey

May 2016

• Certificate in Full Stack Web Development – Rutgers Coding Bootcamp

# Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey

October 2012

• B.A., Information Technology and Informatics, Economics Minor

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Materialize, jQuery, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, JavaScript, Meteor.js, Node.js, React.js, Express, Handlebars, Firebase, MySQL, MongoDB, GIT, Github, Bitbucket the command line

#### **EXPERIENCE**

The God Parent (New Brunswick, NJ)

2016

• Building a web application for parents to save where they stored their baby's items with the image and item detail. The parent will grant access to whom they desire and that person can log in to retrieve the location of things without reaching out to the parent.

# Can I Eat This? (New Brunswick, NJ)

2016

- With a team of three I built a web application for users with food allergies. The users can search the UPC's of packaged foods to get the ingredients and common allergens to determine whether it's safe from them to eat. I was responsible for the product search functionality once the UPC is scanned or entered by the user using Food Essentials API, JavaScript, AJAX, Express routing, and HTML5
- https://github.com/jahdasha/CanIEatThis
- https://canieatthisapp.herokuapp.com/

## Marvel-Superhero-Database (New Brunswick, NJ)

2016

- With a team of three I web app that allows users to search Marvel characters and retrieves their movie and comic book information.
- I was responsible for the Marvel comic search functionality, the embedding of Marvel Database results using the Marvel API, JavaScript, AJAX jQuery, and HTML5
- https://github.com/jahdasha/Marvel-Superhero-Database
- http://marvelsuperherocentral.herokuapp.com/#

## PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

SHI International Corp, Inside Account Manager (Somerset, NJ) T-Mobile, Retail Sales Associate (Belleville, NJ) Tiffany & Co., Sales Service Professional (Parsippany, NJ) April 2013 – Present September 2012 – April 2013 October 2012 – December 2012